learnersedge.com 2019-03-22

# Privacy Policy

**Learners Edge™, LLC Privacy Policy**

**Effective Date:** August 21, 2018

This Learners Edge, LLC Privacy Policy explains our practices, defines our users’ (“ **you** ” or “ **your** ”) privacy options, and describes how your information is collected and used by Learners Edge, LLC (“ **we** ,” “ **us** ,” “ **our** ,” or “ **Learners Edge** ”). 

**By using the Learners Edge website or any of our applications, products, services, features, tools, or resources, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.**

This Privacy Policy, along with our **_Terms of Use_**, governs your use of the Learners Edge website at http://www.learnersedgeinc.com/ (“ **Site** ”), our online portal, our mobile application and any information we may access through social media platforms, including but not limited to, Pinterest, Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn, and Twitter. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, we will refer to all of these access points as the Learners Edge system (“ **System** ”). 

We reserve the right to modify this policy from time to time and will mark new versions with a corresponding effective date. We recommend you visit the Site to review any changes in our practices. Your continued use of the System constitutes your agreement to our then-current Privacy Policy.

Our System may contain links to other websites. These websites may have privacy policies different than our Privacy Policy. The System may also contain certain social media icons or widgets. Although you can view the material we have linked to, you may have to create an individual account or register to use these third-party social media sites to use interactive features. Any interaction on social media websites is governed by the terms of use and privacy policy of the particular platform.

**What Information is Collected?**

We may collect personal information from you on our System, or through any other digital or personal communication between you and the System. Information collected by us may include information such as your name, email address, phone number, and physical address. The System may also collect general information about your technology interface or preferences (such as the type of browser used or the files requested). Additionally, we may collect information regarding the websites you visit and other information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

The information we may collect includes, but may not be limited to:

  * Your contact information, such as your first name, last name, phone number, and email address, to register to receive our course catalogue, newsletter, and other company related updates, promotions, and materials from us; to submit an inquiry through our customer service staff, course instructors, or live chat feature; and to register and participate in webinars and workshops;
  * Your username and password in order to register to create an account;
  * Dates of relicensure, state of licensure, undergraduate and graduate institutions, graduation year, and other relevant information pertinent to your education, qualifications, and licensure.
  * Your education history and specialty areas in order to provide relevant course offerings and to update your transcripts;
  * Other personal information, such as date of birth, gender, and other information required for conducting business with universities in order to provide the System;
  * The last four numbers of your social security number as required by state departments of education;
  * Your payment information in order to enable you to purchase course offerings and sign up for payment plans;
  * Your transaction history relating to the use of our products and services;
  * Information regarding your browser and other technical specifications required to use our Site;
  * Computer data or files, often called “cookies,” which may be sent by your web browser and stored on an individual computer to allow our server to “recognize” you through the navigation of the Site and to perform certain functions, such as saving your passwords and your personal preferences regarding the use of the web site;
  * Computer data files, often called “web beacons” that are collected from emails or links on third-party sites that allow our server to evaluate the popularity of those links or the information contained in emails or on third-party sites; and
  * Your IP address, which is a number automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use this information to measure our website traffic, diagnose problems with our server, administer our Site, analyse trends, improve the site, and to help provide a more personalized experience.

**Children Under the Age of 13**

Our Site and System are not designed for children, and we do not knowingly collect information from any person under the age of 13.

**How is User Information Used and Shared?    **

We collect information about you in order to provide you with services and products, and also to collect information that is necessary for the System to work properly. We use personal information about our users for a variety of purposes related to our business, including but not limited to: 

  * Allowing you to receive information from us regarding Learners Edge products or services;
  * Allowing you to register for an account and to enable your access to a course and course transcripts;
  * Sharing with relevant university partners in order to provide the System to customers;
  * To enable communication with and provide class rosters to course instructors;
  * To process payments and to set up payment plans;
  * To share information with your selected academic partner;
  * Tracking information about your visits to our Site or use of the System to allow us to provide better service;
  * Using certain online preferences in the aggregate across all users to evaluate the System and develop additional products and services to offer;
  * Sending or initiating direct marketing programs, such as newsletters or information about new products or services we are offering;
  * Contacting you regarding an inquiry on the System that you have initiated;
  * Using content from social media platforms where you discuss our products or use a hashtag related to our products;
  * Providing information about your usage or preferences to our third-party vendors and providers; and
  * Other purposes necessary to carry out our obligations under this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use.

We may share information, in the aggregate, regarding your online browsing preferences to evaluate our products or allow the third parties we work with to better serve our users. We will not share personally identifiable information in these instances, other than as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may provide user information to third-party service providers or vendors for purposes of, including without limitation, initiating direct marketing programs on our behalf, data tracking, maintenance or development of our System, development of online products, services, or customer service, or new product development, or other contracted promotional opportunities provided to our users. **We will not share or sell your information with third parties to directly market their products to you.**

We may share this information with any subsidiaries, licensees, suppliers, distributors, affiliates, assigns, successors, or other related entities and their respective owners. We may also share your personal information in connection with law enforcement requests or in response to investigations, subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, or as otherwise required by law.

**Business Transfers**

We may also disclose your information to a third party as part of reorganization or a sale of the assets of Learners Edge, or its subsidiaries or divisions.  Any third party to which Learners Edge transfers or sells the System or related assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us.

**Behavioral Advertising**

We may also use third-party vendors, such as Google Analytics, to advertise to our users online. These third-party vendors may display Learners Edge product advertisements on other websites based on your internet usage. More specifically, these vendors may use first-party cookies, third-party cookies, and other tracking technologies, including but not limited to Google Analytics, Hotjar, Facebook Pixel, Facebook Custom Audience, Facebook Connect, Google Adwords, and others, together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to the Site or another site affiliated with Learners Edge products or services. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising by using Google’s Ads Settings.

**How is User Information Protected?**

We maintain administrative, physical, and technical safeguards for all user information collected in our System. All information provided to Learners Edge is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We also protect account information by placing it on a secure portion of our Site that is only accessible by certain qualified employees of Learners Edge. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.

**How Can Users Limit Information Collected?    **

By providing information to us or using our System, you are consenting to our use of your data as outlined in this Privacy Policy.  

While we work hard to use and disclose our users’ personal information only for the purposes identified above, you can choose not to provide personal information or limit the personal information obtained by us as follows:  

  * You may have your contact information removed from our marketing lists to inform users of new or relevant products, services, and special offers by clicking on the _unsubscribe_ link in any communication received from us, or by emailing us info@LearnersEdgeInc.com
  * You may limit the collection of “cookies” through your browser settings. However, this may disable our ability to provide you with the most relevant products or information regarding the System; and
  * You may limit the ability of Google Analytics to track your online activity, as outlined in the “Behavioral Advertising” section.

**Access To The Personal Data We May Hold About You:**

You can ask us for the specific data that we hold, by contacting us at the information provided below.

Upon request (per the noted methods above), we will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data that we keep about you, within a month (proof of your identity may be required). We will provide the information without any charge.

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data erased, rectified, amended, or completed.

We reserve the right to refuse to provide a copy of your personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal. We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data. Upon your request and to the extent your request does not compromise our privacy or security policies; we will update and correct personal information you have provided to us. If you wish to update your information, you may do so by sending us an e-mail that identifies the information you with to have updated.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code § 1798.83 permits users that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us via the Site. At this time, our website does not respond to Do Not Track signals.

**Contacting Us**

For additional information pertaining to our Privacy Policy, please contact:  

            Learners Edge, LLC

            10523 165th St. West

            Lakeville, MN 55044

You can also send an email to: [info@LearnersEdgeInc.com](mailto:info@LearnersEdgeInc.com)
